A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 8, Accession 2018:011 FA1552
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1983-2015; 1
  - Mepkin Abbey - Dedication of the Saint Francis Retreat Center and Father Francis Kline Memorial Chapel, 2013 (Box 32, Folder 211)
  - Mercy Corps - National Committee on North Korea Policy Salons, 2012-2014 (Box 32, Folder 212)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Luce Center, 1983-1996 (Box 33, Folder 213-215)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Symposium on American Art, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 216)
  - Milwaukee Art Museum - Curator Position (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 33, Folder 217)
  - Monastic Interreligious Dialogue - Hospitality and Dialogue between Christian and Muslim Traditions, 2004-2014 (Box 33, Folder 218)
  - Monastic Interreligious Dialogue - Hospitality and Dialogue between Christian and Muslim Traditions - Gethsemani II, 2002 April 16-21 (Box 33, Folder 218)
  - Montana State University - "Political Portraiture in the United States and France during the Revolutionary and Federal Eras" Conference, 2014-2015 (Box 33, Folder 219)
  - Morehouse College - Howard Thurman Papers Project (Renewal), 2009-2014 (Box 34, Folder 220)
  - Morehouse College - Howard Thurman Papers Project (Second Phase), 2004-2013 (Box 34, Folder 221-223)
  - Morehouse College - Howard Thurman Papers Project (Additional Support), 2003-2013 (Box 34, Folder 224)
  - Morgan Library and Museum - "Matthew Barney Drawings" Exhibition and Catalog, 2012-2014 (Box 34, Folder 225)
  - Multicultural Alliance - Sharing Our Faith Traditions 2009 Retreat, 2008-2013 (Box 34, Folder 226)
  - Museum of Biblical Art - Symposium and Book on Biblical Art and Liturgical Practices, 2007-2013 (Box 35, Folder 227)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, San Deigo - "Ellsworth Kelly: The Figure/Ground Paintings, 1958-1965" Exhibition and Catalog, 2001-2014 (Box 35, Folder 228)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston - "West, Copley, Trumbull: American Revolutionary Paintings in a Transatlantic World" Exhibition and Catalog, 2009-2014 (Box 35, Folder 229-230)
  - National Council of Churches - Global Ecumenical Theological Institute, 2012-2014 (Box 35, Folder 231)
  - National Gallery of Art - "George Bellows, 1882-1925" Exhibition and Catalog, 2010-2014 (Box 35, Folder 232)
  - National Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice - "A Worker Justice Reader", 2009-2014 (Box 36, Folder 233)
  - National Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice - Expand Committee's Program for Seminary Students, 2005-2014 (Box 36, Folder 234-235)
  - National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian Institution - Registrar and Exhibition Design Expenses (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 36, Folder 236)
  - National University of Singapore Foundation - "Religion and the Politics of Development: Priests, Potentates, and Power" Conference, 2013-2014 (Box 36, Folder 237)
  - Nelson-Atkins Museum of Art - Curatorial Assistant and Electronic Access (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 36, Folder 238)
  - New Hampshire Humanities Council - Shifting Ground: Religion and Civil Life in America Program, 2006-2013 (Box 37, Folder 239)
  - New Haven International Festival of Art and Ideas - "613 Radical Acts of Prayer" Liz Lerman Dance Exchange Project, 2006-2013 (Box 37, Folder 240-241)
  - New Museum - "Chris Burden: Extreme Measures" Exhibition and Catalog, 2012-2014 (Box 37, Folder 242)
  - New Orleans Museum of Art - Emergency General Operating Support after Hurricane Katrina, 2006-2014 (Box 37, Folder 243)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts - "Season of Cambodia" Festival, 2012-2013 (Box 38, Folder 245-246)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts, Hugh Lane Municipal Gallery of Modern Art - "Patrick Ireland Retrospective 2003" Exhibition and Catalog, 2001-2010 (Box 62, Folder 401-402)
  - New-York Historical Society - American Art Curator, 2009-2011 (Box 62, Folder 403)
  - New-York Historical Society - Assistant Curator (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 37, Folder 244)
  - New-York Historical Society - Collecting 20th Century Material, 1995-2005 (Box 62, Folder 404)
  - New-York Historical Society - Curatorial Position, 2006-2009 (Box 62, Folder 405)
  - New-York Historical Society - "Life's Pleasures: The Ashcan Artists' Brush with Leisure" Symposium and Panel Discussion, 2007-2009 (Box 62, Folder 406)
  - New-York Historical Society - "Nature and the American Vision: Masterworks of Landscape at the New-York Historical Society" Exhibition, 2005-2010 (Box 62, Folder 407)
  - New-York Historical Society - September 11th: History Responds Initiative, 2001-2010 (Box 62, Folder 408)
  - New-York Historical Society - "The World of Asher B. Durand: The Artist in Antebellum New York" Symposium, 2006-2010 (Box 62, Folder 409)
  - New York Theological Seminary - Center for World Christianity, 2011-2014 (Box 38, Folder 247-248)
  - Newark Museum - Collection-Related Positions, Computer Software Licenses, and Fire Alarm System (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 63, Folder 410)
  - Newark Museum - "Shaping Utopia: Geometric Abstraction in the Americas" Exhibition and Catalog, 2008-2010 (Box 63, Folder 411-412)
    New title of grant: "Constructive Spirit: Abstract Art in South and North America, 1920s-50s"
  - Newcomb Art Gallery, Tulane University - "Women, Art, and Social Change: The Newcomb Pottery Enterprise" Exhibition and Catalog, 2011-2014 (Box 38, Folder 249-250)
  - Noguchi Museum - Catalog and Digitize the Photographic Archives, 2007-2011 (Box 63, Folder 413)
  - Noguchi Museum - Catalog and Digitize the Photographic Archives - Photography Digitization Project (Box 63, Folder 413)
  - North Carolina Museum of Art - Curators, Collection Research, and Travel (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 38, Folder 251)
  - North Carolina Museum of Art - Research and Travel, 2003-2009 (Box 38, Folder 252)
  - Oblate School of Theology - Pastoral Leadership Development Program for Lay Women, 2005-2011 (Box 39, Folder 253)
  - Oblate School of Theology - Pastoral Leadership Development Program for Lay Women (Renewal), 2009-2014 (Box 39, Folder 254)
  - Orange County Museum of Art - "John McCracken: A Retrospective" Exhibition and Catalog, 2013-2015 (Box 39, Folder 255)
  - Orange County Museum of Art - "Siah Armajani: Citizen Artist" Exhibition and Catalog (Rescinded and Cancelled), 2012-2014 (Box 39, Folder 256)
  - Otis Art Institute - "Doin' It in Public: Feminism and Art at the Woman's Building" Exhibition and Catalog, 2010-2011 (Box 39, Folder 257-258)
  - Overseas Ministries Study Center - Artists in Residence Program, 2007-2013 (Box 39, Folder 259)
  - Overseas Ministries Study Center - Artists in Residence Program (Renewal), 2009-2013 (Box 39, Folder 260)
  - Oxford University Press - Grove Encyclopedia of American Art, 2007-2011 (Box 40, Folder 261)
  - Pace University - "Patrick Ireland Retrospective", 2007-2010 (Box 40, Folder 262)
  - Parrish Art Museum - Debt Reduction (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2011 (Box 40, Folder 263)
  - Parrish Art Museum -Travelling Exhibitions, 2009-2012 (Box 40, Folder 264)
  - Parrish Art Museum -Travelling Exhibitions - Checklists (Box 40, Folder 264)
  - Partners for Sacred Places - Program to Help Seminaries Sustain Campus Buildings and Increase Economic Self-Sufficiency, 2010-2014 (Box 40, Folder 265)
  - Partners for Sacred Places - Program to Help Seminaries Sustain Campus Buildings and Increase Economic Self-Sufficiency - Why Should We Spend Money On Our Building When There Is So Much Need In the World?, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 265)
  - Partners for Sacred Places - Training Program on Congregational Partnerships and Resources, 2006-2013 (Box 41, Folder 266-269)
  - Peabody Essex Museum - Native American Art Collection Database, 2009-2011 (Box 41, Folder 270)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - American Sculpture Study Center, 2005-2010 (Box 41, Folder 271)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - American Sculpture Study Center - 200th Anniversary Gala (Box 41, Folder 271)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - American Sculpture Study Center - Untitled Disk (Box 41, Folder 271)
  - Pennsylvania State University - Online Wizard for Assessing Women and Men in STEM (AWE) Project Website, 2009-2011 (Box 41, Folder 272)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - "Bruce Nauman: The Tropical Gardens," 2009 Venice Biennale, 2008-2011 (Box 41, Folder 273-274)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - Benjamin Latrobe Furniture, 2010-2012 (Box 42, Folder 275)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - "George Inness in Italy" Exhibition and Catalog, 2010-2011 (Box 42, Folder 276)
  - Phillips Collection - Fire Damage Repairs, 2010-2011 (Box 42, Folder 277)
  - Phillips Collection - "Georgia O'Keeffe: Abstraction" Exhibition and Catalog, 2008-2011 (Box 42, Folder 278)
  - Phillips Collection - Jacob Lawrence Migration Series Project, 2005-2010 (Box 42, Folder 279)
  - Pisano/Chase Catalogue Raisonne Project, Inc - William Merritt Chase Catalog, 2003-2010 (Box 42, Folder 280)
  - Pittsburgh Theological Seminary - Center for Business, Religion, and Public Life, 2004-2013 (Box 43, Folder 281-282)
  - Portland Art Museum - Northwest Art Curator Position (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2011 (Box 43, Folder 283)
  - Portland Museum of Art, Maine - Chief Curator (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 43, Folder 284)
  - Price Tower Arts Center - "Prairie Skyscraper: Frank Lloyd Wright's Price Tower" Exhibition and Catalog, 2003-2006 (Box 43, Folder 285-286)
  - Prima Civitas Foundation - Global Lansing "Getting Started" Program, 2012-2014 (Box 43, Folder 287)
  - Princeton University - Chinese Rare Book Project, 2002-2010 (Box 44, Folder 288)
  - Project Pericles, Inc. - "Debating for Democracy (D4D) on the Road" Workshops, 2011-2012 (Box 44, Folder 289)
  - Project Pericles, Inc. - Debating for Democracy (D4D) Workshops, 2013-2014 (Box 44, Folder 290)
  - Public Radio International - "The World" Coverage of Religion and International Affairs, 2011-2014 (Box 44, Folder 291)
  - Public Radio International - "The World" Asia Coverage, 2011-2014 (Box 44, Folder 292)
  - Public Religion Research Institute - Research Impact of Religious Pluralism, 2010-2014 (Box 44, Folder 293-294)
  - Purdue University - Religion in China, 2005-2010 (Box 45, Folder 295)
  - Queens Library Foundation - Asian Materials and Programming for the International Resource Center, 2007-2010 (Box 45, Folder 296-297)
  - The Quiet in the Land, Inc. - "The Quiet in the Land: Art, Spirituality, and Everday Life, Luang, Prabang, Lao PDR (2004-2008)", 2008-2014 (Box 45, Folder 298)
  - Religions for Peace - General Operating Support, 2005-2013 (Box 45, Folder 299)
  - Religious Formation Conference - "Engaging a Challenging Future: The Call to Transformation of Religious Life in the U.S." Workshops, 2010-2013 (Box 45, Folder 300)
  - Reconstructionist Rabbinical College - Multifaith Rabbi Training, 2007-2013 (Box 46, Folder 301-303)
  - Reconstructionist Rabbinical College - Multifaith Rabbi Training - Abraham's Children: Jewish Students, Muslim Students, Roman Catholic Students (Box 46, Folder 301-303)
  - Norman Rockwell Museum - Salaries of Exhibitionists Positions (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 46, Folder 304)
  - Rubin Museum of Art - Tibetan Art History Publications, 2011-2014 (Box 46, Folder 305-306)
  - St. Mary's Seminary and University - Graduate Program on Church Ministries, Ecumenical Institute of Theology, 2006-2013 (Box 47, Folder 307-308)
  - St. Mary's Seminary and University - Survey Graduates of the Ecumenical Institute of Theology, 2010-2013 (Box 47, Folder 309)
  - St. Paul School of Theology - Interfaith Academy for Emerging Religious Leaders and Religious Professionals, 2006-2013 (Box 47, Folder 310-311)
  - St. Vladimir's Orthodox Theological Seminary - Arvo Part Concert and Lecture Series, 2012-2014 (Box 47, Folder 312-313)
  - San Antonio Museum of Art - General Upkeep of American Art Collection, 2011-2014 (Box 48, Folder 314)
  - San Antonio Museum of Art - Reinterpret and Reinstall American Art Collection, 2013-2014 (Box 48, Folder 315)
  - San Diego Museum of Art - "Behold America! Art of the United States from Three San Diego Museums" Collaborative Travelling Exhibition, 2007-2014 (Box 48, Folder 316)
  - School for Advanced Research on the Human Experience - East and Southeast Asia Residential Fellowship, 2010-2014 (Box 48, Folder 317-319)
  - Seabury-Western Theological Seminary - Education Program Celebrating Federation with Bexley Hall Seminary, 2012-2014 (Box 49, Folder 320)
  - Seabury-Western Theological Seminary - Strategic Alliance with Bexley Hall Seminary, 2010-2013 (Box 49, Folder 321)
  - Search for Common Ground - Reframe Public Conversation in the United States about Islam and Muslims, 2011-2014 (Box 49, Folder 322-323)
  - Seminary Consortium for Urban Pastoral Education (SCUPE) - Theological Education Program for Latino Pastors, 2008-2012 (Box 49, Folder 324-325)
  - Smithsonian American Art Museum - Senior Curator, Part-Time Exhibition Specialist, Part-Time Program Assistant Positions (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 49, Folder 326)
  - Society for the Arts in Religions and Theological Studies (SARTS) - National Network of Scholars, Graduate Students, and Artists, 2008-2014 (Box 49, Folder 327)
  - South Pacific Association of Theological Schools (SPATS) - Strengthen Libraries of Theological Colleges in Oceania, 2004-2013 (Box 50, Folder 328)
  - Starr King School for the Ministry - Master of Divinity Degree in Multi-Religious Understanding, 2005-2014 (Box 50, Folder 329-330)
  - Starr King School for the Ministry - Multi-Religious Engagement, 2008-2014 (Box 50, Folder 331)
  - Syracuse University - Religion, Media, and International Relations Program, 2006-2014 (Box 50, Folder 332-333)
  - Syracuse University - Religion, Media, and International Relations Program - Old and New Media Conference: Keynote: Lawrence Pintak, 2009 April 2 (Box 50, Folder 332-333)
  - Syracuse University - Religion, Media, and International Relations Program - Old and New Media Conference: Panel 3, 2009 April 3 (Box 50, Folder 332-333)
  - Syracuse University - Religion, Media, and International Relations Program - Old and New Media Conference: Panel 4, 2004 April 3 (Box 50, Folder 332-333)
  - Tanenbaum Center for Interreligious Understanding - 2007 Bosnia Conference, 2007-2013 (Box 50, Folder 334)
  - Tanenbaum Center for Interreligious Understanding - Case Studies on Religious Peacemakers, 2010-2014 (Box 51, Folder 335-337)
  - Tanenbaum Center for Interreligious Understanding - Peace-Making Initiative, 2004-2013 (Box 51, Folder 338)
  - Tate - "Roy Lichtenstein" Exhibition, 2011-2014 (Box 51, Folder 339-340)
  - Theological Consortium of Greater Columbus - Program in World Religions and Inter-Religious Dialogue, 2009-2013 (Box 52, Folder 341)
  - Tides Center - Center for Digital TV and the World's Journalism Training Program on Asia Coverage, 2010-2014 (Box 52, Folder 342)
  - Tides Center, Beatitudes Society - Summer Fellowships Promoting Justice and Reconciliation, 2009-2013 (Box 52, Folder 343)
  - Unicode Consortium - Tangut Script, 2013-2014 (Box 52, Folder 344)
  - United Theological Seminary of the Twin Cities - National Program in Religion and the Arts, 2005-2013 (Box 52, Folder 345-346)
    Contains material related to the Out in Gospel Program grant (2013).
  - United Theological Seminary of the Twin Cities - Out in Gospel: Respecting, Reconciling, and Celebrating Gifts Program, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 347)
  - University of British Columbia - Conference on Knowledge Sharing for the Development of Economic Zones in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 2013-2014 (Box 53, Folder 348)
  - University of British Columbia - Visit by International Experts to Economic Zones in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 2014-2015 (Box 53, Folder 349)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Collaborative Research Seminar on Urban Culture and Social Development in Twentieth-century Shanghai, 1991-2003 (Box 53, Folder 350)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Digital Cultural Atlas of Religions in China, 2003-2014 (Box 53, Folder 351-352)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Digital Cultural Atlas of Religions in China (Renewal), 2007-2014 (Box 54, Folder 353-354)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Sustainable Engineering through Green Design, Manufacturing, and Social Infrastructures Program, 2006-2014 (Box 54, Folder 355-356)
  - University of California, Davis - Population and Development in Contemporary China: A Spatial Analysis, 1993-2003 (Box 54, Folder 357)
  - University of California, Santa Barbara - Environmental Science to Solutions Initiative, 2007-2014 (Box 55, Folder 358-359)
  - University of California, Santa Barbara - Religion in Global Civil Society, Orfalea Center, 2008-2014 (Box 55, Folder 360-361)
  - University of Chicago Divinity School - Chicago Forum on Scholarship in Theology and Religion, 2003-2013 (Box 55, Folder 362)
  - University of Denver - Religious Leaders and Conflict Management in Deeply Divided Societies, 2007-2014 (Box 56, Folder 363-364)
  - University of St. Mary of the Lake, Mundelein Seminary - Faculty Development for Ecumenical and Interfaith Education, 2006-2013 (Box 56, Folder 365)
  - University of Southern California - Religion on the Move: Crossing Borders, Setting Boundaries, 2010-2014 (Box 56, Folder 366)
    An initiative to enhance journalistic and scholarly attention to religion and international relations.
  - University of Virginia - Tibetan and Himalayan Historical GIS Project, 2006-2015 (Box 56, Folder 367)
  - University of Washington - Religion and Human Security Program, 2007-2014 (Box 57, Folder 368-369)
  - University of Washington - Summer Institute for Chinese Studies Librarianship in the Electronic Environment, 2008-2014 (Box 57, Folder 370)
  - University of Wisconsin - Handbook of Southeast Asian Economics Conference, 2012-2014 (Box 57, Folder 371)
  - Vanderbilt University Divinity School - Religion and the Arts in Contemporary Culture, 2007-2014 (Box 57, Folder 372-374)
  - Vanderbilt University Divinity School - Religion and the Arts in Contemporary Culture - RACC Video Clips (Box 57, Folder 372-374)
    1. Andy Statman Trio - Song title unknown
    2. Andy Statman and Ricky Skaggs - Bluegrass Stomp
    3. Leslie Rodriguez, John McClure, Michael Lehman - If I Had a Hammer
    4. Sam Lorber- Blood of the Working Man (Yiddish worker's song)
    5. Justin Rosolino and Divinity Band - Higher Ground
    6. Stephen Mason and Divinity Band - Sunday, Bloody Sunday
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Update and Revise ADVANCE Portal Website, 2011-2013 (Box 58, Folder 375)
  - Virginia Theological Seminary - Program to Foster Understanding between Christian and Muslim Communities, 2008-2013 (Box 58, Folder 376)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum - Senior Curator, Decorative Arts Curator, and Curatorial Assistant Positions (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2013 (Box 58, Folder 377)
  - Wake Forest University - Multicultural Studies Program, 2008-2013 (Box 58, Folder 378-379)
  - Washington University, St. Louis - Interdisciplinary Environmental Clinic, 2007-2014 (Box 58, Folder 380-381)
  - Wesley Theological Seminary - Missional Theology Programs for a Multi-Religious World, 2007-2013 (Box 59, Folder 382-384)
  - Westminster Choir College of Rider University - Catalog Research Materials in Sacred, Choral, and Organ Music in Talbott Library, 2001-2005 (Box 59, Folder 385)
  - WGBH Educational Foundation - Extraordinary Women Engineers Initiative, 2007-2014 (Box 59, Folder 386)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art - Senior Library Assistant and Part-Time Archivist (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 59, Folder 387)
  - Wichita Art Museum - Subsidize Salaries and Avoid Staff Furloughs (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 59, Folder 388)
  - Women's Alliance for Theology, Ethics, and Ritual - Summer Seminary on Feminist Studies in Religion, 2007-2013 (Box 60, Folder 389)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars - Visiting Scholars Program in Religion and Foreign Affairs, 2008-2014 (Box 60, Folder 390)
  - Yale University - Bringing Buildings to Life Program, 2006-2014 (Box 60, Folder 391-392)
  - Yale University, Institute of Sacred Music - Religion and Visual Culture Initiative, 2008-2013 (Box 61, Folder 393-395)
  - Yellowstone Art Museum - 50th Anniversary Publication, 2013-2014 (Box 61, Folder 396)
  - Yellowstone Art Museum - Cash Reserves and Debt Service (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 61, Folder 397)
  - Yeshivat Chovevei Torah Rabbinical School - Jewish Religious Leadership and World Religions, 2008-2014 (Box 61, Folder 398-399)
  - YMCA of Greater New York - Travel Grants for YMCA World Urban Network Meeting, 2007-2008 (Box 62, Folder 400)
- Publications, 1969-2012; 2
  - Henry Luce III Service of Remembrance Program, 2005 November 17 (Box 63, Folder 414)
  - Henry R. Luce: A Mepkin Celebration Commemorating the Centenary of his Birth, 1998 April 4 (Box 63, Folder 415)
  - American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative, undated (Box 63, Folder 416)
  - American Art Review - Special Issue: The Henry Luce Foundation (Volume VII, Number 1), 1995 February-March (Box 63, Folder 417)
  - Henry Luce Foundation at 75 Years, 2012 (Box 63, Folder 418)
  - Luce Foundation: Sixtieth Anniversary, 1936-1996 (Box 64, Folder 419)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 2006-2007 (Box 64, Folder 420)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 2004-2005 (Box 64, Folder 421)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 2002-2003 (Box 64, Folder 422)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 2000-2001 (Box 64, Folder 423)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 1998-1999 (Box 64, Folder 424)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 1996-1997 (Box 64, Folder 425)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 426)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 427)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 428)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 429)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 430)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 431)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 65, Folder 432)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Highlights, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 433)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 434)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 435)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder 436)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 65, Folder 437)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 438)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 439)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 440)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 441)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 442)
  - Henry Luce Foundation Annual Report, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 443)
- Audio-Visual Material, 1992-2001; 3
  - Princeton Theological Seminary Presents: The Henry Luce III Library Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1992 June 2; VHS (Box T1)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Partnership for Tomorrow: New Leaders for a Changing Asia 18:30, United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, undated; VHS (Box T1)
  - A Tree by the River (17 minutes), Mepkin Abbey, undated; VHS (Box T1)
  - Luce Center for the Global Church -- Building Introduction, Presbyterian College and Theological Seminary, 2001 May 14; VHS (Box T1)